{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147508641","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147508641"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153136"," gameId":" f317fa99-c1e6-4669-aa49-0328bb07b78b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147524253","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147524253"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153136"," gameId":" f317fa99-c1e6-4669-aa49-0328bb07b78b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147529954","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147529954"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153136"," gameId":" f317fa99-c1e6-4669-aa49-0328bb07b78b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147536669","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147536669"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153136"," gameId":" f317fa99-c1e6-4669-aa49-0328bb07b78b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147542529","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147542528"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153136"," gameId":" f317fa99-c1e6-4669-aa49-0328bb07b78b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147548334","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147548334"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153136"," gameId":" f317fa99-c1e6-4669-aa49-0328bb07b78b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147566675","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147566674"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153136"," gameId":" f317fa99-c1e6-4669-aa49-0328bb07b78b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147566792","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147566792"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153136"," gameId":" ec97dbd6-82cb-4230-885a-26d3bfa71bbb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MINNE"," userResponse":" MINNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:T..T.all.10.rand.say.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147571801","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147571801"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153136"," gameId":" ec97dbd6-82cb-4230-885a-26d3bfa71bbb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.mc.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147577461","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147577461"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153136"," gameId":" ec97dbd6-82cb-4230-885a-26d3bfa71bbb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147583693","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147583611"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153136"," gameId":" ec97dbd6-82cb-4230-885a-26d3bfa71bbb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147598252","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147598252"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153136"," gameId":" ec97dbd6-82cb-4230-885a-26d3bfa71bbb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:T..T.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147613058","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147613058"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153136"," gameId":" ec97dbd6-82cb-4230-885a-26d3bfa71bbb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sakima aliishi na wazazi wake na dada yake wa miaka minne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147660386","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147660386"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153136"," gameId":" 2893c6dc-bb5b-4cf6-a3b6-339928c5d3dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147669556","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147669555"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153136"," gameId":" 2893c6dc-bb5b-4cf6-a3b6-339928c5d3dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147685091","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147685091"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153136"," gameId":" 2893c6dc-bb5b-4cf6-a3b6-339928c5d3dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" Q"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147688745","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147688745"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153136"," gameId":" 2893c6dc-bb5b-4cf6-a3b6-339928c5d3dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147695852","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147695852"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153136"," gameId":" 2893c6dc-bb5b-4cf6-a3b6-339928c5d3dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147705468","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147705468"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153136"," gameId":" 2893c6dc-bb5b-4cf6-a3b6-339928c5d3dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147735740","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147735740"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153136"," gameId":" 2893c6dc-bb5b-4cf6-a3b6-339928c5d3dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147746153","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147746153"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153136"," gameId":" 2893c6dc-bb5b-4cf6-a3b6-339928c5d3dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147756995","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147756995"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153136"," gameId":" 2893c6dc-bb5b-4cf6-a3b6-339928c5d3dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147759214","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147759213"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153136"," gameId":" 2893c6dc-bb5b-4cf6-a3b6-339928c5d3dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147771022","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147771022"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153136"," gameId":" 2893c6dc-bb5b-4cf6-a3b6-339928c5d3dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147772266","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147772266"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153136"," gameId":" 2893c6dc-bb5b-4cf6-a3b6-339928c5d3dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147776509","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147776508"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153136"," gameId":" 2893c6dc-bb5b-4cf6-a3b6-339928c5d3dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147788586","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147788586"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153136"," gameId":" 2893c6dc-bb5b-4cf6-a3b6-339928c5d3dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147794867","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147794867"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153136"," gameId":" 2893c6dc-bb5b-4cf6-a3b6-339928c5d3dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147808073","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147808073"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153136"," gameId":" 2893c6dc-bb5b-4cf6-a3b6-339928c5d3dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" X"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-1..20.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550147810387","data":{"timestamp":" 1550147810387"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190214_153136"," gameId":" 2893c6dc-bb5b-4cf6-a3b6-339928c5d3dd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-1..20.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}